Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Now there's a nice tooth.
（立花(たちばな)）結構 きれいじゃん
I'll add it to my collection.
とりあえず
コレクションに入れといてやるよ
That's a dentist's son for you.
（ヤンキーＡ）
オッ 出た！ 歯医者の息子
Hey, Tachibana.
（米倉(よねくら)）
立花さん 何本 集まりました？
How many do you have there?
You mean in my collection?
（立花）ああ コレクション？
まだ100本は いってねえけど…
Not quite one hundred, but...
（計(けい)）強(つえ)え…
He's tough.
こっちの歯ぁ…
これもグラグラしてんなぁ！
This tooth feels a little loose too.
I'll take it!
もらっとくぜ
（うめき声）
Such ruthlessness...
（計）
超冷酷… こんなヤツいるんだ
There really ARE guys like this.
All right, then.
（立花）まあ いいや
１年坊は あしたまでに10万な
The tenth grader can bring me
one hundred thousand yen tomorrow.
10万 持ってこいや
One hundred thousand yen, got that?
One hundred thousand yen?!
You've got to be kidding me!
10万？ 冗談じゃない
Who has that kind of money? Not me!
そんな金あるか
持ってねえっつうの！
Oh man, what should I do?
どうする？ どうする？
やる？ こいつと？
Fight? Him?!
Me versus him?!
こいつと 俺が？
I... I won't pay you.
ぜ… 絶対 払わねえ
Just when I thought...
（計）元の生活に帰ってきた
ああ？
（計）…て思った途端
I had my old life back...
なんで こうなるんだよ！
Why does this happen to me?
That Means at the Time...
Now for breaking news at
the scene of the incident.
（リポーター）
現場から事件の続報です
High School Boys Missing in the Subway
A Mysterious Adult Magazine at the Scene
Now for breaking news at
the scene of the incident.
High School Boys Missing in the Subway
A Mysterious Adult Magazine at the Scene
We still don't know the whereabouts of
the two missing high school boys,
その後 消えた２人の高校生の
行方は 一向に分かりませんが―
High School Boys Missing in the Subway
A Mysterious Adult Magazine at the Scene
but take a look at this.
ご覧ください
このヘアヌード写真集が―
But take a look at this.
This adult magazine was found on the platform.
ホームに落ちていたのです
Jeez, this is so embarrassing.
（計）超恥ずかしい 俺…
It's okay.
だ… 大丈夫
ちゃんと マヨネの味もパンの味も
するじゃねえかよ
Mayonnaise still tastes like mayonnaise,
and bread still tastes like bread.
Milk
Mayonnaise still tastes like mayonnaise,
and bread still tastes like bread.
Milk
Even the milk...
牛乳だって…
They ran that way, and then the train arrived,
and I lost sight of them.
（男性）
あっち側まで走ってったんですけど
電車が来ちゃって見えなくなって…
I'm alive.
（計）生きてる
I made it back alive!
生きて帰ってきた 俺は
（西(にし)）多分 俺の考えでは―
Probably. The way I see it,
本体…
オリジナルは本当に死んでる
the original really is dead.
ここにいる人間は
ファクスから出てきた人間なんだよ
The people who are here
came out of a fax machine.
What?
When you go home, you shouldn't
talk to anyone about this.
（西）帰っても ここのことは
誰にも話さないほうがいいぜ
どうせ 信じてもらえないし
They wouldn't believe you anyway.
What do you mean, fax?
（計）何が？ ファクス？
I mean, we're copies.
（西）ああ… コピーだ
Gantz can be pretty sloppy.
ガンツって
かなり いいかげんなヤツだから
Once, a man who came here found
his original alive when he went home.
前にいた おっさんは
帰ったらオリジナル死んでなくて…
Oh, well.
まあ いっか
（計）あっ… 消えた
He vanished.
I guess...
（西）とりあえず
（計たち）あっ…
I'll just have to kill one of you.
（西）今から この中の１人を殺す
…な～んてね
Just kidding!
ハハハハッ… ビビってんなぁ
You should've seen the look on your faces.
But seriously, you shouldn't
speak to anyone about this.
いいか？
誰にも話さないほうがいいぜ
Otherwise, your head will go boom!
頭 “バーン！”だからな
（加藤(かとう)）出ていった
He left?
（計）あっ 開いた
The door opened.
出られた
We made it outside.
（計）あっ… まあいいや
このまま帰るか
Okay...
Shall we go home?
Hey, Kei, maybe you should
let her borrow those clothes?
（加藤）計ちゃんさ その服
貸してやったほうがよくない？
（岸本(きしもと)）あっ…
あっ… そっか
Oh, right.
いいよ
Here.
ありがとう
Thanks.
（岸本）あっ 来た！ タクシー
There's one. Taxi!
Hey!
（加藤・計）お～い！ お～い！
（岸本）タクシー！
（加藤）おい！
Taxi!
Hey!
やっぱ見えてねえのか…
I guess that means people still can't see us?
あっ 止まった
He stopped.
We must look strange in these outfits.
俺たち 怪しいよな 格好
We can go home.
帰れるんだ
Just a moment ago, we were...
ついさっきまで 俺たち…
I don't want to think about it right now.
（加藤）今は考えたくない
（岸本）うん…
Yeah...
（岸本）じゃ 服 ありがとう
Thanks for letting me borrow your clothes.
Your name?
な… 名前…
Why are you blushing?
なんで そこで赤くなんだよ？
I'm...
（岸本）私…
Kei Kishimoto.
岸本恵(けい)
Why do you look so happy just because
he asked for your name?
（計）そっちも名前聞かれて
なんで うれしそうなんだよ？
Kei?
ケイ？
俺と同じ名前じゃん
She's got the same name as me.
She was majorly stacked.
すんげえ巨乳だったよなぁ
（生徒）あ～ この乳 反則だよな
These tits should be outlawed.
They're just wrong!
（生徒）やらしすぎ
（計）お前 巨乳好きだよな
You like 'em big, don't you?
お前もだろう？
So do you!
So did you see the anime that
started on BS yesterday?
（松村(まつむら)）そういや
昨日 ＢＳで始まったアニメがさ
I bet it'll be really big.
あれ 絶対ブレークするよ
Even if I tried to tell them about yesterday...
昨日のこと
こいつらに話してもなぁ…
（松村）なあ 玄野(くろの)
Hey, Kurono...
I'm kind of in a bind right now.
俺 今ヤバイんだよな…
（計）何が？
With what?
Yonekura, in the eleventh grade,
has been hitting me up for money.
俺 カツアゲ食らってんだよね
２年の米倉に
So what?
（計）だから 何だよ？
I can't even buy my anime magazines.
アニメ雑誌も買えなくてさ
知らねえっつうの
（ドアの開く音）
As if I care?
Hey, it's your pal Mr. Yonekura.
（米倉）
ウイ～ッス！ 米倉さんだぞ
How ya doin', Matsumura?
元気か？ 松村
あっ はい…
Fine...
（計）あ～あ…
やっべえのに捕まったな 松村
You've been bagged by
a real creep, Matsumura.
What? Where am I?
あれ？ ここって…
Oh, yeah.
あっ… そっか
That's right.
そっか… 私 自殺したんだっけ
I committed suicide.
あっ はい…
（岸本の母親）しおり？
Hello?
Shiori? You're finally home!
やっと帰ってきた
携帯 なんで つながんないの？
Why didn't you answer your cell?
Something awful's happened.
えっ…
（母親）大変なのよ！ 実はね…
Come straight to the hospital.
あっ… 今から病院 来て
（岸本）しおりじゃ…
This isn't...
Come straight to the hospital.
It's Yamauchi General Hospital.
（母親）山内(やまうち)総合病院なんだけど…
Stay calm when I tell you this.
Mom, I'm...
お母さん 私ね…
You know how to get here, right?
Kei...
（母親）恵が…
お姉ちゃんが お風呂で倒れたのよ
Your big sister fell in the bathtub.
Mom, I'm alive!
（岸本）お母さん… 私 生きてる
（母親）
あっ… 大丈夫よ　生きてる！
Don't worry, she's alive.
えっ？
（母親）さっき意識が戻ったの
She just regained consciousness.
本当よ　すぐ退院できるって
That's right. She can be discharged right away.
The people who are here
came out of a fax machine.
ここにいる人間は
ファクスから出てきた人間なんだよ
We're copies.
コピーだ
Shiori?
（母親）しおり？
This is Shiori, right?
しおりよね？
えっ… 誰？
ちょっと あんた 誰？ 誰なの？
Who?
Who is this? Who is...
（男性）
死ぬぞ こんなとこで寝てたら
You'll catch your death if you sleep here!
High School Students Missing in the Subway
It was on this very platform that
two high school students
（リポーター）
え～ ここのホームで
２人の高校生が―
線路に落ちた人間を
助けたあと―
High School Students Missing in the Subway
suddenly disappeared after helping
a man who had fallen on the tracks.
こつ然と 姿を
消してしまったのです
High School Students Missing in the Subway
This isn't funny!
（加藤の叔母）
冗談じゃないよ！
This isn't funny!
He came home soaking wet!
ずぶぬれで帰ってきたんだからね
I'm sorry.
すいません
迎えに行くつもりだったんですけど
I was going to meet him at school.
Rain's very dirty.
（叔母）雨ってのはね 汚いんだよ
別に洗濯しなきゃなんないでしょう
You have to wash the clothes separately!
You've got to be mindful of such things.
そのぐらい
気を遣ってもらわないとね
After all, you are just a couple of freeloaders.
あんたたちは居候なんだよ！
I know.
分かってます
（叔母）ホントに もう…
For Pete's sake!
Do the two mysterious high school
students even exist?
兄さんも あの女も
勝手に駆け落ちして
My brother and that woman
had to run off and get married,
Do the two mysterious high school
students even exist?
My brother and that woman
had to run off and get married,
Did the police investigation uncover
any new developments?
Have two kids, and then up and die!
Did the police investigation uncover
any new developments?
High School Students Missing in the Subway
have two kids, and then up and die!
Did the police investigation uncover
any new developments?
勝手に
子供２人もつくって…
High School Students Missing in the Subway
have two kids, and then up and die!
I'm sorry, the police haven't made
any announcements as of yet.
（リポーター）
え～ 警察からの発表は
まだ何もありません
High School Students Missing in the Subway
They didn't even think about
the burden I'd have to bear.
I'm sorry, the police haven't made
any announcements as of yet.
They didn't even think about
the burden I'd have to bear.
I'm sorry, the police haven't made
any announcements as of yet.
しかし こちらをご覧ください
（歩(あゆむ)）うん？
They didn't even think about
the burden I'd have to bear.
But take a look at this.
They didn't even think about
the burden I'd have to bear.
This is a plastic umbrella left at the scene.
（リポーター）こちらが
現場に落ちていたビニール傘です
This is a plastic umbrella left at the scene.
（いとこ）ステーキかぁ…
200グラムぐらいにしとこうかな
We're having steak? I guess
I'll go with two hundred grams.
（いとこ）
俺 今日あんまり入んねえ
I'm not that hungry today.
Okay, keep an eye on the house for me.
（叔母）じゃ お留守番 頼むわよ
（加藤）あっ はい
Yes, Ma'am.
（いとこ）
マ… ママ 勝(まさる)君たちも連れてっても
Mom, aren't you going to take Masaru and...
（叔母）ダメよ！
No!
（歩）兄ちゃん
（加藤）うん？
Masaru...
High School Students Missing in the Subway
It's not police evidence?
（キャスター）
警察の証拠品では
ないんですか？
High School Students Missing in the Subway
No, they aren't sure whether this is even a case,
まだ 事件かどうか
はっきりしてませんので
No, they aren't sure whether this is even a case,
so they say this isn't even worth
considering as evidence just yet.
これも 証拠品というほどの物では
ないんだそうで…
Masaru...
兄ちゃん…
That's my umbrella.
僕の傘だ
I'll be getting the pay from
my part-time job soon.
（加藤）
もうすぐバイト料上がっから
ステーキ食いに行こうな
When it comes, let's go out for steak.
あれ 好きだったのになぁ
（加藤）えっ？
I liked that umbrella.
My friend said that "A.K." looked cool,
友達がね
“Ａ・Ｋ”ってカッコイイって
so I told him that you'd carved
the initials in with a box cutter.
だから 教えてやったの
“兄ちゃんが カッターで
彫ってくれたんだ”ってさ
兄ちゃん 昨日 何してたの？
Masaru, where were you yesterday?
Did you leave my umbrella in the subway?
あの傘
地下鉄で落としちゃったの？
What's wrong, Masaru?
どうしたの？ 兄ちゃん
An eyewitness claims that one of
the boys was tall and muscular,
（リポーター）
目撃者の証言では―
ひとりは
背が高い がっちりした体つきで
and the other was of medium height
and build but didn't look very reliable.
もうひとりは
ちょっと頼りない感じの高校生で
中肉中背だったということです
It appears that the unreliable one
dropped the adult magazine.
（リポーター）
この頼りない感じの学生のほうが
ヘアヌード写真集を―
落としていったものと
見られておりまして―
警察では これを手がかりに
行方を追っています
The police are using this as a lead
to uncover their whereabouts.
Kato?
加藤君？
Hey, did you say what I think you said?
おい 今 もしかして
超ナメた口利いたか？ ああ？
もう 後戻りできねえぞ
やっべえなぁ…
Oh, shit. There's no turning back now.
（松村）ご… 5,000円ですよね？
Five thousand yen, right?
（米倉）ふざけんな てめえ！
１万つったろう　このオタク野郎！
Are you kidding me? I said
ten thousand, you fucking nerd.
ど… どうしましょうか？
What do you want me to do?
“どうしよう”もねえんだよ
おいおい… ナメてんのか？ 俺を
What do you think? Hey, are you trying
to yank my chain here?
え～ だって 持ってないし…
But I don't have that kind of money.
（米倉）うん？
じゃ そっちのヤツにもらえよ
So get the money from him.
（計）なんで俺が…
（米倉）おい 松村…
Why should I...
Hey, Matsumura...
こいつにタッチすれば あとの金は
こいつから もらうからよ
If you tag him, I'll hit him up
for the rest of the money.
玄野…
Kurono, I'm sorry.
ごめん
（計）えっ？
What?!
（米倉）
よ～し 松村 じゃ 帰っていいぞ
All right, you're free to go, Matsumura.
（松村）あっ… はい！
（計）お… おい！
Okay!
Hey!
Class has started.
じゅ… 授業 始まって…
知らねえよ そんなの
Like I care!
な… なんで俺が
（米倉）別に～…
Why me?
No reason.
なんとな～く ムカつく てめえの目
You have this look in your eyes
that pisses me off.
放課後まで待ってやる
５万だ　５万用意しとけ
I'll wait until school's over.
Bring me fifty thousand yen.
Fifty thousand.
（教師）
おい そこ！ 何ば しよっとか？
もう 授業始まっとるばい
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?
Class has started!
Is the look in my eyes that bad?
俺 目つき悪いんかな？
（松村）だってさ…
タッチするしかなかったじゃん
Come on!
The only way out was for me to tag you.
You're my friend, right?
お前 友達だろう？
友達じゃねえよ てめえなんか…
You're definitely not my friend.
Friends?
友達か…
（松村）玄野 うんこ？
Kurono?
Are you taking a dump?
ああ 腹 調子悪い
My stomach hurts.
Is he the one you want me to rough up?
そいつ？ シメてほしいってヤツ
Yeah.
そうッス
（立花）ふ～ん… なんで？
I see. Why should I?
（米倉）いや…
なんかムカつくんスよ こいつの顔
Something about his face pisses me off.
かもなぁ… ムカつくかも
Yeah, I can see how it'd piss you off.
But why?
だから なんでだよ！
Hey, Tachibana! I brought him.
（ヤンキーＢ）
立花さん 連れてきましたよ
Who's that?
誰？ そいつ
（ヤンキーＢ）空手部の
この間のバカの先輩ッスよ
He's the senior of that idiot in the karate club
we hit up last time.
I don't care what else you do, but you keep
your hands off our club members.
（部員）ほかは関係ないけど
ウチの部員には手ぇ出すな
（部員）聞いてんのか？ ああ？
Did you hear me?
Return all the money you took
from our tenth graders.
ウチの１年から取った金 全部 返せ
（計）
ラ… ラッキー　俺 逃げられるかも
Lucky!
I might be able to get away.
はぁ？
なに戯言(たわごと) 言ってんだ？ こいつ
What? What kind of nonsense is that?
（部員）
そこにいるヤンキーじゃないヤツ
帰っていいぞ
You, the one who isn't a punk.
Go on home.
（計）
うわ こんなヤツになりてえかも
I wish I could be as cool as him!
C'mon! Get up!
（立花）オラッ！ 立て！
ゲッ… 超見かけ倒し
Boy, was he all bark and no bite.
ハハハハッ… 何だよ 弱(よえ)え！
What a wimp!
よいしょっと…
Okay...
Hey, would you look at that? Your tooth is loose.
おらよ…
あらぁ この歯 グラグラしてっぞ
もらっとくわ
（うめき声）
I'll take it from you.
（立花）結構 きれいじゃん
That's a nice tooth!
I'll add it to my collection.
とりあえず
コレクションに入れといてやるよ
All right, then.
まあいいや
１年坊は あしたまでに10万な
The tenth grader can bring me
one hundred thousand yen tomorrow.
10万 持ってこいや
One hundred thousand yen, got that?
One hundred thousand yen?!
Who has that kind of money? Not me!
10万？ そんな金あるか！
持ってねえっつうの
I... I won't pay you.
ぜ… 絶対 払わねえ
お前 歯ぁ きれいか？
Do you have nice teeth?
虫歯あるか？
Any cavities?
Compared to the Green onion Alien, this guy...
こんなヤツ ネギ星人に比べたら…
あっ… いや… ちょっと
ネギ星人より怖い気がしてきたぞ
Well, I'm starting to get the feeling this guy's
actually scarier than the Green onion Alien.
ウッ…
（立花）おい 勘違い野郎！
You got the wrong idea, kid!
もういっぺん 言ってみろや！
Try saying that again!
Come on! I said, say it again!
オラオラ！ 言ってみろってんだよ
Shit!
（計）
やべえ… なんで使えねえんだ？
このコスプレスーツ
Why can't I use this cosplay suit?
Come to think of it, that girl...
そういや
あの子 すんげえ巨乳だったよな
She was so stacked.
あれ？
なに考えてんだ 俺　こんなときに
Why am I thinking about that
at a time like this?
（立花）オラ！
（殴る音）
やっべえなぁ…
痛み 感じなくなってきたぞ
Uh-oh, I've stopped feeling pain.
ハァ… 会いてえな もう１回
I wish I could see her again.
Hey!
（米倉）あれ～？ ヘヘッ…
やべえんじゃないッスか？
Haven't we gone too far?
He's stopped moving.
動かなくなっちゃいましたよ
こいつ
（立花）ヘヘヘヘッ… オラ…
Hey...
Come to think of it, last night,
she was wearing my clothes.
そういえば ゆうべ
あの子 俺の服を着てたんだよな
That means at the time...
…てことは あのとき
あっ やべえ
Shit.
ああ？ 何だ？ こいつ
（米倉）どうしたんスか？
What the hell?
What's the matter?
He's got a hard on.
（立花）勃起してやがる
ハッ… あれ？ この感覚
Wait!
This feeling!
I think it's starting to work!
ひょっとして いけんじゃねえの？
You got the wrong idea, kid!
I'll fucking kill you!
この勘違い野郎… 死ねや！
オラァ！
I won't pay you.
絶対 払わねえ
何だ？ バカか こいつ
What did you say?
Are you that stupid?
立花さん 殺しちゃっていいッスよ
Tachibana, it's okay to kill him!
Why, you...
て… てめえ
つぶせる　こんな腕！
I could crush this arm!
Should I crush it?
つぶすか？
What are you doing, Tachibana?
I said you could get rid of him.
（米倉）
何やってんスか？ 立花さん
こんなヤツ
やっちゃっていいッスよ
Damn... Let go!
くそ… は… 離せ！ ウッ… ウウ…
You dumb kid!
（米倉）バ～カ 小僧
（立花）ナメてんじゃねえぞ！
Don't fuck with me!
You, the one who isn't a punk.
（計）
そこにいるヤンキーじゃないヤツ
Go on home.
帰っていいぜ
な… 何が起こったんだ？
What the hell happened?
（計）ちきしょう…
（鼓動音）
Damn it!
My hands won't stop shaking!
手の震え 止まんねえ
No way!
（計）ウソ…
マジ？
Is this for real?
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
（加藤）守るべきもの…
恐怖 怒り 焦り 呪縛 暴力
Something to protect.
Fear, anger, impatience, captivation, violence!
That's right. Violence does not
exist only in that room.
そうだ 暴力は
あそこにだけ存在するんじゃない
It's all around us.
すぐそこにも それは ある
あそこだけじゃない
Not just in that room.
Right, Ayumu?
そうだろう？ 歩
Next time: "All Right!"
次回 “やったああああっ”